trembling...
Pjust like a small bird
It's nice to just kick back and relax
Pjust like a small bird.
and watch a bit of TV every now and then.
It is, isn't it?
PEveryone come aboard
Pit'ss
Go for it! Go for it! Choo choo choo!
Why did you change the channel all of the sudden?
It's fine! Comedy King is a funny show!
Mero mero mero mero!
Comedy isn't what it used to be.
Wellnext upi
That's exactly right!
Wow! Great!
Ah, right! Tsubasa-chan's movie should be on now
Huh? Oh, it's not on yet?
Oh! This is a great drama!
That's enough!
Why can't you just stay on one channel?
Go to bed!
Looks like you were kicked out.
well, we should go to bedanyway.
I don't want to! I don't want to!
There's no way I could go to sleep now!
I want to watch TV! I want to!
It's nothing to cry about...
Dream Player
Instead of on TV, you can watch things in your dreams.
In my dreams?
With these disks, you can dream whatever you want
Science Fiction Thiller Historical Drama,
Documentary Soap Opera...
There's a lot!
This one... Oh, you wouldn't be interested in this one.
What wouldn't Ibe interested in?
It's a disk for Moral Instruction.
It's good for you
But, it's the one you'd hate most of all, right?
Don't try to decide for me.
Why shouldn't I want to have a dream that's good for me
so that someday be an upstanding member of society?
That would be nice...
Now, all you have to do is go to sleep.
But it's still too early.p
It emits radio waves that will put you to sleep
You should be fast asleep within ten minutes.
Uh, what?
It didn't even take ten seconds!
Of course...
Get up!
Who are you?
Welcome to the Moral Instructiondream!
Alter-Nobita
you follow my instructions, you'll surely
become an upstanding member of society!
Oh, of course.
Look at that magnificent sunrise!
The early bird gets the worm!
see. This certainly is good for me".
Okay.let's go!
WhWhere?
Joggingof course!
W-Wait! Why should I have to go jogging!?
A healthy spirit requires a healthy body!
Strengthening your body is the first step!
can't go onThere's no way can keep this up
no good at jogging
If you want to become a better personno more complaining!
If you have the will, it will happen! If you don't, you'll never succeed!
you put your mind to ityou can do any thing!
If
Okay! One, two, three!
The cold means nothing to a strong child!
Nothing cleanses the mind like being doused with cold water!
Time waits for no man!
Quick, dry yourself!
Why do I have to study so early in the morning?
Why put off til tomorrow, when you can do that today?
There's no time like the present!
Time flies like an arrow!
You must not waste the present!
Shut up with that already! I quit!
This dream is no fun! I'm through with this dream!
can't allow that! Once you start a dreamyou must finish it!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
You have to set your sights on something and follow it through!
If you go your whole life changing your
mind you'll never finish any thing!
Shut up!
You're awake already?
What kind of dream was that?
You really shouldn't stop the disk in the middle...
This one! It's about pirates!
I'll become a pirate and go on a great
adventure in search of treasure!
The weather is clear and the waves are high!
This is it! This is the dream I wanted to have!
Aperfect sky and sea
A fine crew of rogues.
Captain Nobita
And a beautiful damselb
Captain Nobita, does Legend Island really exist?
This secret treasure passed down through
generations of the Minamoto family.
feel anxious
Huh? Captain Nobita? Your face is green.
You're the first pirate I've met with seasickness.
feel sick. Every thing is spinning-
Someone give me some water.
It's a ship! It looks like Captian Gian!
I've finally found you, Captain Nobita!
Found you!Found you!"
It's a ship! It looks like Captian Gian!
I've finally found you, Captain Nobita!
Found you!"Found you!"
Gian?
The great pirate known as the Devil of the Sea"!
Fire!
Hurry up!
Hey, that's dangerous! What if one of us was hit?
Ha ha ha! You're so weak!
Cease fire!
Prepare to board!
Captain Nobita!
They're getting closer!
I don't plan to be sunk.
Shizuka, get yourself to a safe place.
Okay.
Men hold them back!
We fight!
He's so cool!
Really?
How's that?
You little..!
No way!
This is it.
It's not over yet!
Wait!
won't let you get away!
How's that?
There's nowhere left to go!
Looks like the tables have turned.
you fall from this height, you're...
finished.
Ha ha! Scary!
A bird in the sky... the blue sky...
I'm falling...!
can't swim! Save me!
Captain Nobita!
guess there are pirates who can't swim, too.
It seems there are pirates who are afraid of heights, too.
Oh, anyway, is this the right way?
Yes, we may have lost the ship, but
still have the secret treasure.
If we keep going this way, it should
only take three days to get there.
Three days!?
I'm sick of being a pirate!
I'm tired, and I'm sore, and I'm sick
and I can't swim, and I hate it, I hate it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Did you give up again?
Being a pirate is silly!
In this day and age, swords and treasures are totally unrealistic.
Science fiction is better for someone from our time.
Yellow Ship Squad has arrived at jumpin point Y3030CBSignal A. Enemy engage line. All-armor.
Signal A. Enemy engage line. All-armor.
All ships, check in.
Roger!
Engage!
This thing is huge!
Commander! It's passed the point!
Hiromura! Keep things under control out here.
break my way in.
Wa ha ha ha!
The foolish fools!
They dare to challenge the great Emperor Suneo?
We shall teach them their place.
You summoned me, Your Highness?
They seem to be trying their best to win.
Yes.
End this farce.
Yes, Your Highness.
Waha ha ha!
Damn, is there no way to beat them?
Nobita? Can you hear me, Nobita?
Princess Shizuka!
We've figured out that ship's weak point.
What?
The ship is surrounded by a strong barrier
To destroy the barrier, you must damage
the ship's central generator.
To do this, you must access the ship's computer.
see. How do I gain access?
You must solve these problems, Nobita!
What!?
believe in you.
Oh, well, three times five is...
Eighteen!
Ahhh!!
What's the deal with this dream?
Pulling out arithmetic like that is unfair!
Who cares about peace in space?
I'm sick of this dream!
Sick of it! Sick of it!
You quit halfway through again?
This difficult science fiction just wouldn't work for me.
Was it really that difficult?
Next, let's try something more simple.
Something with super heroes.
That was quick
Miss Cooking sama, we've assembled all the green peppers.
Well done.
Soon all meals throughout Japan will
be made solely from green peppers!
And thus all Japan's children will cry out in terror!
Oh ho ho ho!
I won't allow that!
What?
Who are you?
I won't allow anyone to disturb the peace of Japan's dinner tables!
Transform!
Kamen Nobita!
"Kamen Nobita"? Pathetic!
Destroy him!
Nobita kick!
You... Green Pepper Missle!
You'd waste perfectly good green peppers?
ill eat them all!
What kind of dream was that?
Welcome back.
That plot was too childish
can't accept a dream that isn't more mature than that.
No matter how many you go throughthey'll
never go exactly they way you want
Instead, why don't you try following through...?
Ah, this is good! A teen drama!
Wait, I'll just watch the last scene.
it's good, then I'll watch the whole thing.
What!?
Noyou can't do that! Stop!
Nobita-kun!
Oh, it's you guys.
Nobita-san!
Don't. After all, I'm a teenager!
Nobita san!
Nobita-kun!
We've grown.
Nobita-san!
understand. Don't say anymore.
Everyone, look at that!
It's so pretty.
That sunset is for us!
It's welcoming us!
Everyone, let's dash into the sunset!
Yeah!
Hurray for youth!
Hey, wait up!
Wait!
You're all too quick!
Hey!
quit!
I'm through with this dream!
I want this dream to end! End Dream!
Huh? It's not ending
Owww! But I'm not waking up!
Why? What's going on!
Doraemon! Doraemon!
Thank goodness. Hey Doraemon, end this dream.
No. The machine is broken.
"Broken"?
Broken. Damaged. You can never leave this dream.
You can never leave this dream.
That can't be.
It's impossible!
have to wake up! I have to open my eyes!
Captain Nobita?
Are you day dreaming?
Huh? What?
Okay, shall we go to Legend Island?
The secret treasure is ours.
This is a dream. A dream.
It's mixed into my other dream!
What are you blathering on about?!
Gian!
What did you say you'd do to me before?
Get him!
Hey, Nobita-kun!
Nobita san!
Hey!
Escape with us!
Where to?
Solve these problems
Solve these
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
Go stand in the hall!
Doraemon!
Oh, boy.
Maybe I went a bit too far.
Huh?
Do you understand now?
No matter what it is, you must choose a goal and follow through.
No matter what it is, you must choose a goal and follow throughYou've been going through Moral Instruction" this whole time.
Huh!? This whole time?
Yes.
The pirates, the science fiction,
the super heroes, and the teenage drama,
it was all a part of the moral instruction dream.
I knew you would eventually grow tired of just moral education.
No way!
In conclusionyou must follow through!
Perserverance pays off!
If you put your mind to it, you can do anything!
What doesn't kill you only makes you stronger!
Yo, good morning!
Good morningis it?
So, how was the moral instruction? No good?
No good, but...
Next time I want to have a dream like dream!
Naturally.